Guide to the Records of the NYU Abu Dhabi Institute AD.RG.024.1
NYU Abu Dhabi, Archives and Special Collections
- Audiovisual Event Files, 2007-2015
  - Program DVDs
    - NYU DTC (1): Lessons from Beyond Vision, Feb. 13, 2011 (Box 5)
    - NYU DTC (2): Are the Actions and Emotions of Music "Out There"?, Feb. 13, 2011 (Box 5)
    - The Science of Sad Sounds [2 copies], Feb. 13, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: David Huron
    - The Nature of Taste, Feb. 13-14, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Paul Boghossian, Barry C. Smith; Charles Spence
    - Magical Arbitrariness, Feb. 14, 2011 (Box 5)
    - Repositioning Islam Through the 99 [3 copies], Feb. 21, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Naif Al-Mutawa
    - Gordon Brown, Feb. 24, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Gordon Brown
    - Beyond the Crash: Overcoming the First Crisis of Globalisation, Feb. 24, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Gordon; Jones, Bruce D. Brown
    - The US, Emerging Powers, and Traditional Threats, Feb. 25-26, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Stephen Krasner; Cheng Li
    - The Theif of Baghdad, Feb. 26, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers:
    - Obama's Health Reform: Is It Doomed? (And What About His Presidency?), Feb. 27, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Rogan Kersh; Robert Shrum; Diane Yu
    - Use and Misuse of Probability, Mar. 1, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Nassim Taleb
    - Housing Middle Income Households in High-Cost Cities: Is There a Role for Government?, Mar. 3, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Micheal White; Talal Al Dhiyebi; Ingrid Gould Ellen
    - Long Distance Networks and World Systems, Mar. 6-7, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Barbara Kowalzig; Walter Scheidel
    - Beliefs, Markets and Empires, Mar. 6, 2011 (Box 5)
    - Commerce and Empire in India: the Centrality of the Hindu Temple, Mar. 7, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: David Ludden
    - Enhancing Economic Development Through Technology, Mar. 8, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Yaw Nyarko, Lakshminarayanan Subramanian
    - On Liturature, Love, and Revolution in the Muslim World, Mar. 10, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Ibrahim Abdel Meguid; Mohamed Al Mansi Kandeel; Rabai Al Madhoun
    - The 'Heart and Mind' of Diplomacy: Twenty-First Century Cultural Diplomacy, Mar. 13, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Cynthia Schneider
    - Moments in Silence, Mar. 15-17, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Ella Habiba Shohat; Amir Moosavi
    - The Stock Market and Corporate Investment, Mar. 16, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Alexander Ljungqvist
    - Women Writers of the Middle East, Mar. 19, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Haifa Zangana, Gloria Jacobs, Judith Miller
    - The Magic of Words [2 copies], Mar. 28, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Anna Deavere Smith; Ruben Polendo
    - Completing the Urbanization Project, Apr. 3, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Paul Romer
    - Markets: A Novel Approach to Assess Sovereign Debt Risk [2 copies], Apr. 4, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Ed Altman
    - Moufida Talatil Tunisie, Apr. 9, 2011 (Box 5)
    - Healthcare Reform in the US [2 copies], Apr. 11, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Nassim Delos Cosgrove; Andrew Rubin
    - The Non-Obsolescence of Liberal Toleration, Apr. 14, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Catriona McKinnon
    - Intel Labs: Staying Ahead of Technology, Apr. 18, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Tanay Karnik
    - 3D Integration Workshop, Apr. 18, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Hai (Helen) Li, Yuan Xie, H. Jonathan Chao
    - 3D Integration (Sessions 1,2,4), Apr. 18-19, 2011 (Box 5)
    - Imagining the Future (Day 1), Apr 20, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Anna Deavere Smith, Gideon Lester
    - Imagining the Future (Day 2-3), Apr. 21-22, 2011 (Box 5)
    - Unifying Arab Awakening, Apr. 20, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Khaled Abol Naga
    - Manarat Al Saadiyat, Apr. 21, 2011 (Box 5)
    - Zeb & Haniya, Merlijn Twaalfhoven and Anani Dodji Sanouvi, Apr. 21, 2011 (Box 5)
    - Salut Cousin!, Apr. 23, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Peter Scarlet, Ella Shohat, Robert Stam, Mo Ogrodnik
    - Music/Voice in Islam, Apr. 28, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Anne Rasmussen; Walter Zev
    - Classical and Quantum Turbulence, May 2, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: K.R. Sreenivasan; Wei. Guo
    - From Angstroms to Light Years, May 02, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: K.R. Sreenivasan
    - A Bicycle Built for Two, May 4, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Rebecca Fiebrink
    - From Angstroms to Light Years (Group Photo), May 5, 2011 (Box 5)
    - Le Grand Voyage, May 7, 2011 (Box 5)
    - The Body as a Weapon, May 8, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Riaz Hassan
    - Translating Shafi's Risala, May 10, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Joseph E. Lowry
    - The Hadhrami Migration, May 31, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Michael Gilsenan
    - A Decade Lost: Locating Gender in US Counter-Terrorism, Sept. 19, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Lama Fakih; Jayne Huckerby; Sari Kouvo, Rahma Abdulkadir
    - A Human Rights Approach to Gender, Counterterrorism, and National Security, Sept. 19, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Margaret Satterthwaite, Jayne Huckerby
    - Portia's Brilliant Legal Strategy, Sept. 22, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Stephen Gillers
    - Panel Paintings From Roman Egypt, Sept. 27, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Thomas F. Mathews
    - An Egyptian Pantheon at the Origin of European Painting, Sept. 28, 2011 (Box 5)
    - Film Screening of "Khan Al Khalili", Oct. 6, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: In collaboration with Abu Dhabi Film Festival
    - What the Global Economy Needs, Oct. 9, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Gordon Brown; Bruce D. Jones
    - A Bottom-Up Approach to the Rebuilding of Somalia: The Azania Case, Oct. 17, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Mohamed Abdi Gandhi
    - The Undispossessed, Oct. 20, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Shamoon Zamir, Yasser Alwan
    - Muslim Americans: Faith, Freedom, and the Future, Oct. 23, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Angela Migally; Dalia Mogahed; Jamillah Karim
    - Producing Public Value Through Cross Sector Social Relationships, Oct. 25, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Ali Al Rahbi; Jamila Khanji; Mohammad Al Jawdar
    - Deepening Research On Cross Sector Partnerships in the Middle East, Oct. 26, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Sonia Ospina; Bethany Godsoe
    - The View from Somewhere: Discourse in the Humanities, Oct. 27, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Philip Weinstein
    - Building Apps For the Social Good of the Arab World, Oct. 30, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Sana Odeh
    - Science and Society Innovation, Nov. 16, 2011 (Box 5)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: John J. Healey
    - A Billion Minds and Lives, Dec. 11, 2011 (Box 6)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Amna Al Marzouqi; Shekhar Saxena; Vikram Patel; Gary S. Belkin
    - World Literature and Translation, Dec. 13, 2011 (Box 6)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Rebecca Johnson; Marilyn Booth
    - Sisters: A conversation with Nadia Benchallal, Sept. 27, 2012 (Box 6)
    - Design and Technology of Integrated Systems in Nanoscale Era, Mar. 26-28, 2013 (Box 6)
    - Experimental Art and the Arab World, May 1, 2013 (Box 6)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Kenneth Goldsmith; Tiffany Malkooti
    - Between Hormuz and Malacca, circa 1599, May 6, 2013 (Box 6)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Jorge Flores
    - The Paradox of Classical Music, May 9, 2013 (Box 6)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Judit Frigyesi
    - Pre-Occupations in the UAE, May 13, 2013 (Box 6)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Daniel T. Potts
    - Trade, History, and Network in the Indian Ocean, Sept. 4, 2013 (Box 6)
  - Program USBs [in process]
    - We are all Corals Now, Sep. 30, 2013 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-001)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Margaret Wertheim
    - The Life We Live and The Art We Make, Oct. 08, 2013 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-002)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Sue Coe; Zena el Khalil; Joanne Savio
    - The Marvelous, Mundane Orient of Abu Zayd and Ibn Battutah, Oct. 10, 2013 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-003)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Tim Mackintosh-Smith
    - The Waterpipe: A Cultural Past Time or a Public Health Threat?, Oct. 21, 2013 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-004)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Wasim Maziak
    - Waterpipe Tobacco smoking, Oct. 21, 2013 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-005)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Kenneth Ward
    - First International Conference on Waterpipe Tobacco Smoking, Oct. 22. 2013 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-006)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Unreadable USB drive
    - Health Inequities in the Arab Region: A Call for Public Policy Reforms, Oct. 23, 2013 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-007)
    - Dark Matter: Evidence, Experiments, and Properties, Oct. 24, 2013 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-008)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: David Hogg
    - 1967 and 2011: Arab Intellectual Responses, Oct. 29, 2013 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-009)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Elizabeth Kassab
    - Why is the UAE a Federation?, Oct. 29, 2013 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-010)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Frauke Heard-Bey
    - Exploring Islamic Art at the Met: A Walking Guide, Nov. 07, 2013 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-011)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Navina Najat Haidar
    - CLEAR WATERS: Flute and Piano Recital, Nov. 09, 2013 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-012)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Celina Charlier; Edmundo Villani-Côrtes
    - Understanding Nabati Poetry: Tools of the Trade, Nov. 11, 2013 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-013)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Saad Abdullah Sowayan; Marcel Kurpershoek
    - Abu Dhabi Reads: The American Granddaughter, Nov. 14, 2013 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-014)
      Program Officiator/Speakers: Joanne Bui; Salwa Mikdadi; Cyrus Patel; Deborah Williams
    - Climate Change: A Failure of Politics?, Nov. 17, 2013 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-015)
    - Beiruti Theater in Action, Nov. 19, 2013 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-016)
    - TURNAROUND: Third World Lessons for First World Growth, Nov. 21, 2013 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-017)
    - Young Voices of Abu Dhabi: Plan 2030, Nov. 23, 2013 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-018)
    - Impossible Citizens: Dubai's Indian Diaspora, Nov. 26, 2013 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-019)
    - Arabic Philosophy within/without the Western Canon, Dec. 04, 2013 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-020)
    - Fifty Years with Mandela: From Lawbreaker to Lawmaker, Dec. 08, 2013 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-021)
    - Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Falcons, and Abbasid Hunting Poetry, Dec.10, 2013 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-022)
    - Muslim World or Ummah? Origins, Content, and Evolution of Pan-Islamic Thought, Dec. 16, 2013 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-023)
    - Humanitarian and Development Aid for the World's Children: Perspectives from the UAE, Jan. 08, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-024)
    - Jan. 08, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-025)
    - Jan. 08, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-026)
    - Jan. 09, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-027)
    - Jan. 11, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-028)
    - Doubt in Islamic Law: Burden or Benefit?, Jan. 12, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-029)
    - Scheherazade's Children, Jan. 14, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-030)
    - Life on the Baynunah River: Abu Dhabi 7 Million Years Ago, Jan. 15, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-031)
    - Jan. 16, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-032)
    - Jan. 18, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-033)
    - Jan. 19, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-034)
    - Jan. 20, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-035)
    - Jan. 25, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-036)
    - Jan. 27, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-037)
    - Jan. 28, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-038)
    - Jan. 30, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-039)
    - Feb. 02, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-040)
    - Feb. 03, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-041)
    - Feb. 05, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-042)
    - Feb. 09, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-043)
    - Feb. 12, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-044)
    - Feb. 18, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-045)
    - Feb. 18, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-046)
    - Feb. 19, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-047)
    - Feb. 20, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-048)
    - Feb. 20, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-049)
    - Feb. 24, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-050)
    - Feb. 25, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-051)
    - Feb. 25, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-052)
    - Mar. 04, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-053)
    - Mar. 06, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-054)
    - Mar. 11, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-055)
    - Mar. 11, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-056)
    - Mar. 13, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-057)
    - Mar. 16, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-058)
    - Mar. 19, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-059)
    - Mar. 30, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-060)
    - Mar. 31, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-061)
    - Apr. 01, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-062)
    - Apr. 01, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-063)
    - Apr. 02, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-064)
    - Apr. 06, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-065)
    - Apr. 14, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-066)
    - Apr. 16, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-067)
    - Apr. 20, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-068)
    - Apr. 24, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-069)
    - Apr. 27, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-070)
    - Apr. 27, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-071)
    - Apr. 28, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-072)
    - May 1, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-073)
    - May 05, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-074)
    - May 08, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-075)
    - May 11, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-076)
    - May 11, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-077)
    - May 12, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-078)
    - May 13, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-079)
    - May 14, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-080)
    - Sep. 29, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-081)
    - Nov. 02, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-082)
    - Nov. 02, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-083)
    - Nov. 03, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-084)
    - Nov. 04, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-085)
    - Nov. 06, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-086)
    - Nov. 09, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-087)
    - Nov. 12, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-088)
    - Nov. 17, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-089)
    - Nov. 22, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-090)
    - Nov. 25, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-091)
    - Nov. 27, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-092)
    - Nov. 30, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-093)
    - Nov. 30, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-094)
    - Dec. 07, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-095)
    - Dec. 08, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-096)
    - Dec. 09, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-097)
    - Dec. 09, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-098)
    - Dec. 10, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-099)
    - Dec. 10, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-100)
    - Dec. 14, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-101)
    - Dec. 15, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-102)
    - Dec. 16, 2014 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-103)
    - Feb. 01, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-104)
    - Feb. 08, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-105)
    - Feb. 10, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-106)
    - Feb. 12, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-107)
    - Feb. 15, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-108)
    - Feb. 16, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-109)
    - Feb. 17, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-110)
    - Feb. 17, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-111)
    - Feb. 17, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-112)
    - Feb. 18, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-113)
    - Feb. 19, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-114)
    - Feb. 19, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-115)
    - Feb. 23, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-116)
    - Feb. 25, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-117)
    - Mar. 01-03, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-118)
    - Mar. 02, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-119)
    - Mar. 03, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-120)
    - Mar. 04, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-121)
    - Mar. 04-05, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-122)
    - Mar. 05, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-123)
    - Mar. 08, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-124)
    - Mar. 08-10, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-126)
    - Mar. 09, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-127)
    - Mar. 10, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-128)
    - Mar. 12-14, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-129)
    - Mar. 15-17, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-130)
    - Mar. 16, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-131)
    - Mar. 16, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-132)
    - Mar. 18, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-133)
    - Mar. 29, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-134)
    - Mar. 31, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-135)
    - Apr. 06, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-136)
    - Apr. 09, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-137)
    - Apr. 11, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-138)
    - Apr. 12, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-139)
    - Apr. 13, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-140)
    - Apr. 14, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-141)
    - Apr. 15, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-142)
    - Apr. 18, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-143)
    - Apr. 19, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-144)
    - Apr. 21, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-145)
    - Apr. 23, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-146)
    - Apr. 26, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-147)
    - Apr. 28, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-148)
    - May 04, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-149)
    - May 07, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-150)
    - May 11, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-151)
    - May 17, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-152)
    - May 18, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-153)
    - May 19, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-154)
    - May 19, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-155)
    - May 20, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-156)
    - May 21, 2015 (Box 7, Folder AD_RG_024_USB-157)